# Robert S. Greenawalt, Jr.

 $Philadelphia, PA~19031\cdot (215)-913-7231\cdot robert.greenawalt29@gmail.com\\ \textbf{Github}: github.com/rsg71~\textbf{LinkedIn}: www.linkedin.com/in/robert-greenawalt~\textbf{Portfolio}: rgreenawalt.herokuapp.com\\ \textbf{Github}: github.com/rsg71~\textbf{LinkedIn}: www.linkedin.com/in/robert-greenawalt~\textbf{Portfolio}: rgreenawalt.herokuapp.com\\ \textbf{Github}: github.com/rsg71~\textbf{LinkedIn}: www.linkedin.com/in/robert-greenawalt~\textbf{Portfolio}: rgreenawalt.herokuapp.com\\ \textbf{Github}: github.com/rsg71~\textbf{LinkedIn}: www.linkedin.com/in/robert-greenawalt~\textbf{Portfolio}: rgreenawalt~\textbf{Portfolio}: rgreenawalt~$ 

Full Stack Web Developer with a degree in business administration and experience working in the financial and legal industries. Highly motivated to create and design web applications using technologies like, MongoDB, React, and JavaScript. Passion for continued learning and a demonstrated ability to adapt to new environments. Fluent in Spanish. Certified by 365 Careers Excel: Financial Modeling and Valuation

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Technologies**: MongoDB, MySQL, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, JavaScript ES5/ES6, JQuery, Handlebars.js, JSON, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Heroku, REST APIs, Bootstrap, Mongoose, Sequelize

Miscellaneous: Windows, Git/Github, Microsoft Suite (Excel)

#### **PROJECTS**

- Table Turner: An application for modern restaurants looking to expedite order fulfillments and place greater emphasis on allergy concerns and special requests from customers
  - Responsibilities: establish database structure, create dynamic menu search, implement Toastify notifications, bring functionality to delete buttons for menu item and table
  - Uses MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Passport.js, bcrypt.js, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React-Bootstrap
  - Deployed: (https://tableturner.herokuapp.com/login) | Repo: (https://github.com/rsg71/Table-Turner)
- Restaurant Finder: Search by restaurant category and state to return a list of results plotted with markers on Google maps
  - Responsibilities: pair Google Maps functionality with search criteria in order to plot results dynamically
  - Uses MySQL, Express.js, Handlebars.js, Passport.js, bcrypt.js, HTML, CSS, Javascript, and Google Maps API
  - Deployed: (<a href="https://findtherestaurant500.herokuapp.com/">https://findtherestaurant500.herokuapp.com/</a>) | Repo: (<a href="https://github.com/rsg71/Restaurant\_Finder">https://github.com/rsg71/Restaurant\_Finder</a>)
- Weather Dashboard: Enter in a city to return current day's weather information and a five-day forecast
  - Responsibilities: enable search bar to make API calls, implement Moment.js, store API data in local storage
  - Uses Javascript, HTML, CSS, Moment.js, Open Weather API
  - Deployed: (https://rsg71.github.io/Weather-App/) | Repo: (https://github.com/rsg71/Weather-App)

### EXPERIENCE

## Morgan, Lewis & Bockius LLP, Philadelphia, PA

Dec 2018 - Aug 2020

### Billing Specialist

- Coordinate and manage all aspects of billing for 12 partners and 80+ clients (GMC, Sysco, Boston Globe).
- Manage the review and distribution of monthly proformas to all assigned partners; verify hourly rates and matter set up
  in accordance with client pricing agreements
- Ensure compliance with rate structures as stipulated in outside counsel guidelines; monitor unbilled balances and accounts receivable in a timely manner

#### MEH Investments, Flourtown, PA

May 2017 - Aug 2017

#### Summer Intern

- Conducted market research, due diligence, and financial analysis of targeted commercial real estate acquisitions to assess viability
- Attended weekly meetings with investors, builders, interior designers, and potential tenants

### U.S. Realty Capital, Conshohocken, PA

May 2014-June 2014

Intern

- Learned financial analysis in underwriting deals including leverage, valuation, proformas, discounted cash flows, and capital markets
- Attended weekly management meetings, lender and client meetings, and on-site property inspections

### **EDUCATION**

University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, PA

- Full-Stack Web Development Program (MERN Stack)

Aug 2020-Nov 2020

**University of Richmond Robins School of Business**, Richmond, VA *Bachelor of Science* in Business Administration, concentration in Finance

August 2014-May 2018

Cumulative GPA: 3.28

• Member of Alpha Phi Omega Community Service Fraternity and Club Rugby Team

University of St. Louis, Madrid, Spain

January 2017-May 2017

Semester Abroad GPA: 3.40

• Relevant courses: Management Science & Operations Management, Information Technology Management